webmakerx.net 2004-10-10

# Privacy Policy

**Regarding Reynolds' responses to the GLB/FTC Safeguards Rule:**

  * For our customers who receive products or services through the Master Agreement, see our Contractual Safeguards Commitment (page 8) in the [Customer Guide](http://my.reyrey.com/).
  * For our customers who receive products or services through an agreement other than the Master Agreement, read our Contractual Safeguards Commitment.
  * View our Frequently Asked Questions: General FAQ and Product-Specific FAQ.  

**Information in this Privacy Statement**  
On this Web page, we describe the commitments The Reynolds and Reynolds Company (“Reynolds”) makes to the privacy of individual consumers. This statement includes: 

  * the general Online Privacy Policy for Websites identified as the property of Reynolds (“Reynolds-branded Websites”), including our Websites for our consumer technologies
  * Reynolds Information Practices for processing individuals’ information, online or off, on behalf of our business clients
  * our contact information, for questions or comments you may have about this statement or our practices

Reynolds business customers, please see our [Customer Guide](http://my.reyrey.com/).

**_Scope of this Privacy Policy_**

  * This Privacy Policy generally applies to Websites that are specifically identified as belonging to Reynolds (“Reynolds-branded Websites”), including this corporate Website, www.reyrey.com. This Privacy Policy also applies to Reynolds-branded Websites for particular Reynolds consumer tech-nologies. Please note that those sites may also post their own privacy policies to describe information practices specific to their products and services.
  * We are the industry leader in providing integrated technologies and services to our business clients—primarily vehicle retailers and manufacturers. Since this Online Privacy Policy only applies to information we collect on our own behalf, it does not apply to information we collect on behalf of our business clients or from our business clients who utilize our hosted applications. To learn more about our overall information practices on behalf of our business clients and on and off the Web, read about Reynolds Information Practices. 
  * Reynolds Websites may display links to Websites controlled by other companies or organizations. Please be aware that Reynolds is not responsible for the privacy practices of those other parties or the content or operation of their Websites.

**_Collection and use of data from Reynolds Websites_**  
**Anonymous information:** We monitor site traffic for administrative purposes—for example, to ensure smooth site traffic flow or to assess what pages on our sites are visited the most and by visitors from which countries or Internet Service Provider (ISP) domains. To do this, our Web servers aggregate the anonymous information that your browser automatically transmits anytime you are on the Web. We do not use this infor-mation to attempt to identify you. We may enlist the services of a third-party Web-statistics service provider, but only under the condition that the service-provider’s use of this anonymous data is limited to providing the services we request.

**Personally identifiable information:** On Reynolds-branded Websites, we collect personally identifiable in-formation only when you choose to provide it to us, such as when you register to use a particular Reynolds consumer technology, submit an employment application, or send us a comment by email. 

  * We only use your personally identifiable information to respond to your communication or provide the product or service you request.
  * We use your personally identifiable information to send you information about other products and services only if you give us express (“opt-in”) permission to do so.

**Cookies:** The only time we use cookies to save information about you is when you are visiting a Website re-lated to a Reynolds consumer technology and you give us express permission to keep a list of the particular products or services you are interested in. We only use this information to respond to you or provide the product or service you requested, or internally, to help us monitor Website traffic and improve our Websites.

**_Disclosures for legal reasons_**  
We may disclose individual information to comply with legal process, such as a subpoena or court order, or to protect or enforce our legal rights.

**_Changes to this Privacy Policy_**

  * If we make any material change to this Privacy Policy, we will provide at least 30 days advance notice on this page and on our corporate home page at www.reyrey.com.
  * If we make any material change to the privacy policy associated with any Reynolds consumer technology, we will provide 30 days advance notice on this page, on our corporate home page at www.reyrey.com, and on the home page and privacy policy page of the particular Reynolds consumer technology. 
  * If we make any material change to a Reynolds privacy policy, previously collected information will con-tinue to be governed by the protections of the privacy policy in effect at the time the information was col-lected. 

**_Changes in ownership_**  
Reynolds may decide to sell, buy, merge, or reorganize businesses to further strategic or business interests. Where a transaction of this kind involves disclosing personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, our practice is to seek appropriate protections consistent with our privacy policy.  

**End of Reynolds Online Privacy Policy**

_**Reynolds solutions for business clients**_  
We are the leading provider of integrated technologies and services that help our business clients—primarily vehicle retailers and manufacturers—maintain vehicle and parts inventories, manage accounting and busi-ness administration, and process sales and service information. In providing solutions to these businesses, a critical part of our job is to support our business clients’ privacy and safeguards objectives. 

_**Safeguarding data**_  
In all aspects of our information practices at Reynolds, online and off, we are committed to implementing and maintaining safeguards appropriate to protect the privacy, security, confidentiality, and integrity of data about individuals. 

We often act as a service provider to business clients. When we receive consumer data from a business client so that we can provide services to that client, we limit our use of the data to the purposes for which our business clients provided the data to us.

We use service providers, too. For example, to improve Web response time, we might arrange for a Reynolds-branded Website to reside on a server owned by a Web-hosting company. In those cases, it is our practice to require that the service providers handle information in a manner consistent with our policies and the commitments we have made to consumers and our business clients.  

_**Compliance**_  
We comply with government privacy and security standards, including: 

  * the Federal Trade Commission’s Privacy and Safeguards Rules implementing provisions of the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Financial Services Moderni-zation Act (for more information, please visit [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/)); 
  * the Telemarketing Sales Rule issued by the Federal Trade Commission (for more information, please visit [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/)); 
  * the Federal Communications Commission’s rules implementing the Telephone Consumer Protection Act (for more information, please visit [http://www.fcc.gov](http://www.fcc.gov/)); 
  * and the Canadian Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (provisions effective Jan. 1, 2004; for more information, please visit [http://www.privcom.gc.ca](http://www.privcom.gc.ca/)). 

Our [Networkcar system](http://www.networkcar.com/) offers vehicle owners a cutting-edge tool for automotive security and maintenance. When you have a Networkcar system installed in your vehicle, you gain Internet access to dynamic automo-tive diagnostic data and location so you can monitor and maintain your vehicle’s location and performance. With Networkcar, your call for roadside assistance authorizes our call center to pinpoint your vehicle’s loca-tion, so that help can find you. Networkcar’s location-based technology also helps locate your vehicle in the event of theft.

View more information about the [Networkcar system](http://www.networkcar.com/) and the measures we take to safeguard the privacy of our Networkcar customers.

email us at [privsec@reyrey.com](mailto:privsec@reyrey.com) or contact us at:  
Director of Privacy  
Legal Department  
Reynolds and Reynolds  
One Reynolds Way  
Dayton, OH 45430 

Tel: (937) 485-9635  
Fax: (866) 246-0507  

_updated on September 16, 2004_
